A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- CKU Reference Files, 1949-1979; 3; 27.6 Cubic Feet
  - Greater - Gregory (Box 20, Folder 157)
    Great Private Collections Greater Williamsport Art Festival Grebeksky, Jack Greek Sculpture Green, Adora Leidecker Green, Ambassador Marshall Green, Gregory D. Green Haven Correctional Facility Greenberg, Benjamin B. Greenberg, Ester (Two Squares Art Gallery) Greene, Arline Livingston Greene, Joel Greene, Theodore R. Greenough, C. P. 3rd Greenough, Mrs. Charles E. Greenrock Play House Greenrock Rugs Greenspun, Joanne Greenwich Country Day School Gregori, Alberto Gregory, Alvin Gregory, Bobby Gregory, Mrs.Yolande
  - Griffin - Grussing (Box 21, Folder 158)
    Griffin, George A. Griffin, George D.J. M.D. Griffin, Harriet Griffin, Michael H. Grimaldi, Mario Grippi, Joseph Gris, Juan Groenzoel Grolier Club Grosshennig, Wilhelm Grosvenor Gallery Grove, Edward R. Grove, Perry E. Grumet, Shiah & Miriam Grundy, Andrew III Grunwald, Julius Peter Grussing, Bon D.
  - Guani - Guffey (Box 21, Folder 159)
    Guani, Alberto Guarini, Mrs. D. Frank Guarnati, Italo Guastella, Nick Guccione, D. J. Guelick, Mrs. M. Guerrero, Jose Guerrero, Leticia Guest, Winston Guffey, Homer L.
  - Guiga - Gutierrez (Box 21, Folder 160)
    Guiga, Chacha Guild Hall Gulezian, H. Aram Gulyas, Mrs. A Gumbel Gurfinkel, Hermann Gurwin, Mrs. Joseph Gutierrez, Therese Dulac
  - Glass Conservation and Restoration, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 161)
    Correspondence re restoration of broken Abraham Lincoln paining on glass by Corning Glass.
  - Guggenheim, 1966-1967, 1975, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 162)
    Correspondence re exhibits and programs at the museum.
  - Haags Gemeentemuseum - Hagen (Box 21, Folder 163)
    Haags Gemeentemuseum Haas, Mrs. Charles D. Hack-Prestinary, Carlos R. Hackley School, The Hadassah Haese, Gunter Hafer, W. W. Jr. Hagen, Mrs. Harry Hagen, Harry
  - Hahn - Halpern (Box 21, Folder 164)
    Hahn, Gerald Margarita Hahn Vidal Hajjar, Eliya Hakone Open Air Museum Halahmy, Oded Halevi, Gabriel Halick, John Hall, G. Elinor Halpern, Ethel
  - Hamada - Hantman (Box 21, Folder 165)
    Hamada, Shoji Hamaker, R. G. Hamer, Marilou Hames, Martin Hamill, Mrs. Barker G. Hamilton, Alexander Hamilton Gallery Hamilton, Hildegarde Hammer, N. V. Hammer, Victor J. Hammond, John G. Hammond Museum Han, Theodore Y. T. Hanno, Eugene Hanns, Rose Hansegger, John K. Hannum, Becky Hansen, Julia Hansen, Laura K. Hansen, Robert Hanson, Bill Hanson, Edward Hanson, Hans Hanson, Mrs. Lowell K. Hantman, Murray
  - Hardie - Harmon (Box 21, Folder 166)
    Hardie, Mrs. I. M. Hardy, C. P. Hargan, Elizabeth Hargroue, Boyd Harithas, James Harlem River Truckmen and Riggers Incorporated Harlow, Marie Harmon, Warren
  - Harr - Harwood (Box 21, Folder 167)
    Harr, Evelyn Harriet Griffin Gallery Harriman, Jannea R. Harrington, Mrs. John Harris, Arthur L. Harris, Godfrey R. Harris, Jack D. Harris, Leon David Harris, Mrs. R. (Sara) Harris, Mrs. Wallace K. Hart, Olive P. Hartert, William H. re Jack J. Hartert Hartford, Larry Hartley, Denise Hartley, Grace Hartley, Marie Hartmann, Olga Harvard University Harvard University Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts Harvey, James N. Harwood, Mrs, Anthony Harwood, M.K.
  - Haskell - Hawkins (Box 22, Folder 168)
    Haskell, Ernest Jr. Haskins, Vernon Hassevelde, Roger Haster, Albert H. Hataburda, C. M. Hatfield, Dalzell Hathaway, Mrs. Ben Haus der Kunst Hausman, Sam Hauswedell, Ernst Hawaii Hawes, Marion Hawkes, Robert E. Hawkins, Ashton Hawkins, Carl R. Hawkins, Rose
  - Hayes - Hayward (Box 22, Folder 169)
    Hayes, David Hayes, Mary Healy Hayes, William Hayman, Frederick (Hayman-Chaffey) Hayman-Chaffey, Susana Hayner, Floyd M. Hayward, Carolyn E. Hayward, Mrs. Dolph
  - Hearsey - Hendrich (Box 22, Folder 170)
    Heasey, Charles Hearst Fund Hebald, Milton Heckel, Siddi Heckscher Museum, The Heeramaneck Galleries Heidman, W. A. Heinrich, Lilly Heise & Zack Held, Al Held, August Helicopters Helie, Mrs. Heller, Mrs. John Helton, Mary Hempel, Kenneth Henderson, Miltne Hendrich, Mrs. Walter G.
  - Henri - Hertzberg (Box 22, Folder 171)
    Henri, Wolf Henry, E. L. Henry, Kirby D. Henry, Patrick Herbert, David Herceg, Davor Heredia, Manuel Herlands, Wendy Herne, Elaine R. Herrick, Edwin R. Herrmann, Ingrid Herron, Nausicaa Herter, Susan Hertzberg, Benjamin
  - Hess - Heyl (Box 22, Folder 172)
    Hess, Mrs. C. K. Hess, Leta English Hessing, Josephine Hester, Mrs. Philip Hetzler, Dr. Florence M. Edwin Hewitt Gallery Heydenryk Heydenryk, Henry Heydenreick, F. Maria Heyl, Tony
  - Hickey - Hinman (Box 22, Folder 173)
    Hickey, Mrs. A. D. Hickey, Mrs. Lee Cole Hickock, Mr & Mrs. G. A. Hicks, Neil M. Hickson, Mrs. Jerome B. Hietala, A. Stanley Hiesz, Alexandre Higgins The High Museum of Art Hiigli, John Hilburn, Charles A. Hildesley, Hugh Hill, Don F. Hill, Loraine J. Hilmer, Edwin Jr. Himmelstein, Paul Hines, Feldreth Hinman, Charles
  - Hirsch - Hitt (Box 22, Folder 174)
    Hirsch, Stephan Hirschl & Adler Hirschl, Norman Hirschhorn, Joseph H. Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden Historical Society of Pennsylvania Hitchner, O. T. Hitt, George H.
  - Ho - Hofstra (Box 23, Folder 175)
    Ho, James C. Hobbss, Frederic Hobby, Theodore Y. Hoberman, Norman Hobi, Monsieur Hobi-Billstein, Mrs. Hochschwender, George A. Hoey, T. G. Hoff-Barthelson Music School Hoffman, Mr. and Mrs. B. M. Hoffman, Emil G. Hoffman, Ernest Hoffman, Hans Hoffmeister, F. S. Hofstra College
  - Hogan - Hook (Box 23, Folder 176)
    Hogan, Mary Hoggart, Winifred Hogle, Richard A. Hokuga Japanese Prints Holen, Norman Holdeman, Ralph Hollis, Howard C. Holman, Lloyd W. Holmes, David J. Holmstock, Toni E. (Atlier Milos) Holtkamp, William J. Homburger, Freddy Homer, Winslow Honda, Eturo Hoober, Sophie Hood, Catherine C. Hood Gallery Hook, E. W.
  - Hopkins - Hopper (Box 23, Folder 177)
    Hopkins Art Center, NAR's gift to Hopkins Center Art Galleries Dartmouth Benefit Exhibit, 1970: Edward Hopper Hopper, William H.
  - Horl - Howe (Box 23, Folder 178)
    Horl, Mrs. Henry Hornaday, William D. Hornor, Mrs. Allen T. Hornung, Mrs. Robert M. Horowitz, Frederic Horowitz, Marcel Horowitz, Nadja Horst, Mrs. R. L. Horton, Carolyn (Carolyn Horton and Associates) Horton, Helen B. Horwin, Louis Horwitt, Will Horwitz, Ruth Hosley, Truxton Houghton, Arthur A. Jr. re Grace Ibingira House, John V. Houston, Contemporary Arts Association of Houston Museum of Fine Arts Hoveyda Howald, Harry J. Howard, Trudy Howard Wise Gallery Howat, Heduro Howe, David A. Library Howe, Oscar
  - Huber - Hull (Box 23, Folder 179)
    Huber, Carlos Hubert, Thomas Hudson Guild Hudson, Joseph L. Jr. (The J. L. Hudson Company) Hudson River Museum Hudson River School Hudson Art Valley Association Huethwohl, Charles Huff, Mrs. E. L. Hughes, E. Burton Hughes, Margaret Hulett, Katherine Hull, John
  - Huber - Hull (Box 23, Folder 0179A)
    Hughes, Mrs. Dewey R.
  - Humidifers - Hurwich (Box 23, Folder 180)
    Humidifiers Hummel, Katherine Hundertwasser, Friedereich Hunt, Conover Hunt, Lady Eucelia S. Hunt, Lynne Bogue III Hunt, William Norris Hunter, Dr. M. J. Hunting World Incorporated Huntington, Agnes L. Huntington, Dr. and Mrs. David Huntington Galleries Hurd, Norman Hurd, Mrs. John Hurlbul, Lucille Hurney, Joseph J. Hurschler, J. L. Hurst, Charles R. Hurwich, Carolyne N.
  - Hutchins - Hyppolite (Box 23, Folder 181)
    Hutchins, Maude Hutchinson, Max Hutchinson, William Leonard Hutton Galleries Huttrer, Dr. C. P. Hyams, Harriet Hyde, J. A. Loyd Hydron Hymans, Diane Hyppolite
  - Hahn Brothers, 1964-1975 (Box 24, Folder 182)
    Correspondence, memoranda, invoices, and receipts for storage and transportation of artworks.
  - d'Harnoncourt, Rene, 1949-1976 (Box 24, Folder 183)
    Correspondence and memoranda on purchases of artwork recommended by d'Harnoncourt and NAR artworks stored at the Museum of Modern Art (MoMA).
  - d'Harnoncourt, Rene, 1949-1976 (Box 24, Folder 0183A)
  - Iavelle - IGAS (Box 24, Folder 184)
    Iavelle, Mary IBEC loans Idle, Ken IGAS
  - Immerman - Inter-American Institute of Fine Arts (Box 24, Folder 185)
    Immerman, David Inaugural Medal, 1975-1976 India, Ghandara Head India Nepal Handloom House Indiana University Art Museum Indiana University Bloomington Industrial Fumigation Ingber, Neil Ingling, Dorothy Innes, James B. Inro Cords Insler, Judith Institute of Contemporary Art, The Institute of Fine Arts Insurance Inter-American Defense College Inter-American Institute of Fine Arts
  - International - Inventory (Box 24, Folder 186)
    International Archive of Art International Art Dealer Association International Art Line Incorporated International Art Market International Art Program, National Collection of Fine Arts International Art Registry Ltd., The International Center of Photography International Committee for Museums International Conference of Police Associations International Foundation for Art Research International Institute for Conservation of Historic and Artistic Works Inukai Inventory
  - Iolas - Ivy (Box 24, Folder 187)
    Iolas, Alexander Gallery Iran Irinyi de Irinyi, Gabor Irvine, Ann Irwin, John C. Irwin, Lem A. Isaacs Gallery Isaacs, Marguerite Evans Israeli Arts and Crafts Center Israel Museum, American Friends of the Instituto Della Enciclopedia Italiana Israel Museum Isirati, Alexandre Italian Emergency Relief Committee Italy Ithaca Iverson, Christina IGAS Ivey, Mrs. W. L. Ivy, Robert H.
  - IGAS, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 188)
    Catalogs for the IGAS series 94, 98-100. Lists of IGAS prints missing from NAR's collection.
  - Insurance - General, 1950-1974 (Box 24, Folder 189)
    Correspondence and memoranda re policies on NAR art.
    See also FAVs.
  - Insurance - Claims, 1950-1974 (Box 24, Folder 190)
    Correspondence, memoranda, invoices and summaries of claims made for damages to NAR artworks.
  - Insurance - Registered Mail Receipts, 1966-1971 (Box 24, Folder 191)
  - Irene Lamp Shades, 1963-1975 (Box 24, Folder 192)
    Correspondence, memoranda, invoices and fabric samples for lamp shades.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - Documents Given to IRS by Howard Bolton, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 193)
    List of art pieces. Catalog sheets.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - General News Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 194)
    Newspaper clippings re Rockefeller wealth and art collection. Information re the IRS Art Advisory Panel.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - General News Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 0194A)
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - Gifts, 1971, 1974, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 195)
    Appraisals of gifts of art given by NAR.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - Gifts, 1971, 1974, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 0195A)
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - IRS Questions, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 196)
    Catalog sheets, photos and purchase information needed to answer an enclosed list of questions. Questions about general practices answered by Carol Uht.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - IRS Questions, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 197)
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - IRS Questions, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 0197A)
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - Picasso, Oedipus and the Sphinx, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 198)
    Correspondence and appraisals of the tapestry to support NAR in the IRS tax discrepancy.
  - IRS Tax Administration Advisory Panel - Venezuelan Collection, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 199)
    Appraisals and lists of artworks at NAR's ranches, Monte Sacro and Palo Gordo.
  - Jack Gallery - Jain (Box 25, Folder 200)
    Jack Gallery Jaclin Stationery Jackson, Fritz Martha Jackson Gallery Jackson, Michael J. Jackson, O. D. Jacksonville Arts Center Jacques, Mariette Jacob, John Jacob, Marion Jacobsen, Hans Jacobwitz, Mrs. P. Jacoby, Lefevre Jade Treasures Jaeger, J. F. Jaeger, Richard Jaffee, Cynthia Jagu, Brigite Jain, Lakshmi
  - Jambor - Jamison Galleries (Box 25, Folder 201)
    Jambor, Mrs. Louis (Violet E.) James, Mrs. C. T. James, Herbert L. James, Paul Jamuieson, Francis Jamison Gallieries
  - Janetz - Janusz (Box 25, Folder 202)
    Janetz, E. Sidney Janis Gallery Jannson, Mrs. Janusz, Mrs. Edward Janusz, Irene
  - Japan House Gallery - Jawlensky (Box 25, Folder 203)
    Japan House Gallery Japan International Art Promotion Association Japan - Pablo Picasso Art Exhibit Japan Society, Inc. Japanese Jarboe, Evelyn Jarboe, Joann Jarrell, Lou Ethel Jawlensky, Alexej
  - Jeanes - John & Mable Ringling Museum (Box 26, Folder 204)
    Jeanes, B. J. Jefferson, J. Thomas Jeffries, Ruth Jenkins, Schuyler D. Jennen, Eve C. Jerome, Nathan S. Jette, Ellerton Jeunet, Roger Jewelry Jewish Community Council of Bangor, Maine Jewish Community Center of Washington, D.C. Jewish Museum Job Applications Jock's Trucking Jock's, Temple Hills Maryland John P. John John & Mable Ringling Museum of Art
  - Johnson - Jones (Box 26, Folder 205)
    Johnson, Mrs. Addison Johnson, Daniel LaRue Johnson, Daryl D. Johnson, Eastman Johnson, Elaine Johnson, Elroy Johnson, Halle Johnson, Jeanne D. Johnson, Lou Johnson, Philip Johnson, Ray Johnson, William Johnston, Emily Jones, Betsy Jones, Colleen M. Jones, Mrs. Edd Jones, Edward Powis Jones, Frances Folin Jones, Mrs. Howard S. Jones, Jameson Jones, Julie Jones, Lloyd B. Jones, Ora Bess
  - Jonnsan - Justh (Box 26, Folder 206)
    Jonnsan, Burt Jordan, Johnnie Jordy, William H. Louis Joseph Inc. Josephson, Arthur Journal American Judd, Mrs. Edward N. Jr. Juffe, Mel Juharos, Stephan Junec, Lorris Just Above Midtown Gallery Justh, A.
  - Kadison - Karlsen (Box 26, Folder 207)
    Kadison, Mrs. Milton Kadokawa Publishing Company Kahnweiler, Daniel-Henry Kaiden, Nina Kalhagen, Alfred O. Kalman, Ronald J. Kamitatu, Cleophas, President of Leopoldville Kandinsky, Wassily Kane, Bob Kaplan, Bernard Kaplan, Joan Kaplan, Joyce Karafyllakis, Antonio L. Karetnikov, Dimitri Karlberg, Evelyn Karlis, Tirca Karlsen, Elisabeth
  - Karo - Kaufman (Box 26, Folder 208)
    Karo, Gigi Karshan, Donald H. Karter, Patricia Karver, Jerome Kasak, Nikolai Kaston, Maryna Kasuba Katonah Gallery Kattan, Ghassan Katz, Alex Katz, Hilda Kaufman, Jane
  - Kawashima - Kazimierz (Box 26, Folder 209)
    Kawashima Kay, Orlean Glass Kazimierz, Almakiewicz
  - Keating - Keizo (Box 26, Folder 210)
    Keating, W. R. Kecks, (Caroline and Sheldon) Kee, Tan Kian Keel, Frank Keiner, David Keiss, Edward Keizo Saji's Collection
  - Kelemen - Keru (Box 26, Folder 211)
    Kelemen, Mathias E. Kellad, Daniel Keller, Margaret Lehman Keller, Mrs. Theodore J. Kelly, June Kelly, Dennis Kelly, Leon Kelsey, Dorothy Kendall, John A. Kendis, Rachel Kent, Jean Kentucky, University of Coe Kerr Gallery Kerekes, Mr. and Mrs. Gabriel T. Kerschner, Mrs. Ira Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer Kerton, Sudjana Keru, Arthur B.
  - Ketterer (Box 26, Folder 212)
    Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer Munchen Ketterer, Roman Norbert
  - Keystone - Kezal (Box 26, Folder 213)
    Keystone Helicopter Corp. Kezal
  - Khan - King (Box 27, Folder 214)
    Khan, Muhammad I. Khanlian, John Kidd, Barbara S. Kidder, Jane Kiehart, Paul Kiep, Walther Liesler Kieta Enterprises Kilbride, Bob Kilim Rugs Kim, Henry Kimball, Edward Kimball, Mrs. William F. King, Andrew A. King, Antionette King, Mrs. David G.J. King, Antiguidades, Ltd. King, John R. King, Richard E. King, Robert
  - Kipp - Kittrie (Box 27, Folder 215)
    Kipp, Luman Kirchner, E. L. Kirkpatrick, Russel G. Kiro, Boris Kirstein, Lincoln Kissinger, Henry Kite, George Kittle, Marina Kittredge, Ray Lash Kittrie, Nicholas N.
  - Klass - Knutson (Box 27, Folder 216)
    Klass, Enid Kleeman Galleries Klejman, J. J. Klemin, Diana Klickstein, Mrs. Murray Kline, Fred Klinghoffer, Clara Klintworth, H. Fred Kluver, J. Wilhelm Knapp, J. C. Knight, Elmira H. Knight, Joan Knoedler & Co. (M. Knoedler & Company, Inc.) Knowles, Belle Knox, Seymour H. Knutson, Raymond J.
  - Ko - Kornblee Gallery (Box 27, Folder 217)
    Ko, Wen-Chen Kobashi, Yasuhide Kodiak Historical Society Koehnline, W.A. Koffarnus Kohan & Epner Kokobayl, Allen Kolber, Warren F. Kolin, S. Kollander, David L. Kollek, Teddy Kolthoff, Ester L. Komor, Mathias Kondo, Stephan Kohipol, Hannah I. Konrad, Anton J. Konrad, Tony Kontny, Mrs. E. S. Kooncy, Sara Korhonen, Arne A. Korn, George F. Kornblee Gallery
  - Koscherak - Kovac (Box 27, Folder 218)
    Koscherak, Roland Koshiba, H. T. Koshkin-Youritzin, Victor Kosloff, Elliot Kostich, Jean Kovac, J. J.
  - Krabbes - KTCA-TV (Box 27, Folder 219)
    Krabbes, Alfred Kragler, Wilfried Kramer, H. Kransler, Ron Kraushaar Galleries Kraushaar, Antoinette M. Krause, Bjorn O. Krauss, Anthony Kreeger, David Lloyd Krieger, Seymour Kriendler, Doris Kronen, Gabrielle Kronen Gallery Kronheim, Emil Kruger, Louise Kruml, Mrs. George Krystyna KTCA-TV
  - Kublik - Kyncl (Box 27, Folder 220)
    Kubik, Kamil Kubin, Irma Kuebler, Paul C. Kuhn, Brenda Kulawik, Kurt Kulhanek, James C. Kulikowski, Jan Kulkowitz, Harry Kunheim, Dr. Hugo Kunin, Morris H. Kunitz, Stanley Kunsthalle Bern, Switzerland Kunstnernes Hus Kupris, Valdis Kurland, David E. Kyi, Ru-Tao Kykuit Stone Kyncl, Dr.-Ing. Milan
  - Kennedy Galleries, 1959-1975 (Box 28, Folder 221)
    Correspondence, memoranda and catalogs for artworks that NAR may have been interested in purchasing.
  - Kennedy Galleries, 1959-1975 (Box 28, Folder 222)
  - Kootz Gallery, 1948-1965 (Box 28, Folder 223)
    Correspondence re purchases, loans on approval, interests, and exhibits.
  - Kykuit Collection Cataloguing Project, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 224)
    Memoranda and lists of objects. This project was completed by Sara Austen.
  - Labiosa - Lalouette (Box 28, Folder 225)
    Labiosa, Wilfred Labrie, Rose Lacher, Sam Lachman, Winifred W. Ladas, Lois (American Crafts Council) Ladd, John L. La Farge, John LaForest, Lillian J. Lake, Frederio E. Laky, Les Lalouette, Madame R. L.
  - Lamb - Lane (Box 28, Folder 226)
    Lamb, Adrian Lambert, James G. Lambright, Elizabeth Lamotte, Bernard Lampl, Nanette Lamps Lancaster, Rose Mary Landais, H. Landau, Mitzi Lande, Henry C. Landell, Joan Landy, Zita Lane, Alvin S. Lane, Bobby Lane, Richard
  - Langenthal - La Nuova (Box 28, Folder 227)
    Langenthal International Corp. Langlais, Bernard Langley, J. Alex Langley, Mrs. William C. (Jane) Langseth, Arne F. Lanningham, Virginia B. La Nuova
  - Lapham - Lattermann (Box 28, Folder 228)
    Lapham, Donald Lapides, Mrs. Marton M. Larcada Gallery Larcada, Richard K. La Riviere, Harry R. Larson, John H. La Russa, Ignacio Laserte, Robert C. Lasky, Stephen J. Lassiter, Charles Lastra, Luis Laterza, Parodi Lattermann, Jutta L.
  - Laudisio - Lazzarotto (Box 28, Folder 229)
    Laudisio, Giovanni Laug, Minerva Lauritzen, Elin Laursen, Earl J. Lauter, Margarete (Galerie Lauter) Lavaggi, Rene Lavaggi, Robert Lavatelli, Carla Laventhol, Hank Lawrence, Camille Lawrence, David L. Lawrence, Larry R. Lawy, E. Claire W. Layne, Frances Layne, Tom Lazar, Otton Lazarnick, George Lazzari, Pietro Lazzaro, Paul Lazzarotto, Lucia
  - Leber - Lemons (Box 29, Folder 230)
    Leber, Detlev LeBlanc, Benedict Lebouc, Y. Lebron, James Lebron Brothers Le Comte, Mia Lee, Bud Lee, Eva Lee, John K. C. Lee, Marshall Lee, Niwa Lee, Oliver Justin Lee, Robert J. LeFebre Gallery Leger Leger, Sidney Legere, Jon Legge, Howard Lehe, Georgette C. Lehman College Lehman-Haupt, Hellmut Lehn, Ralph J. Leich, Jean Ferriss; Leichtman, Bertha Leino, Lillian Le Marchant, Michael Lemmy, Lemons, Dixie
  - Lenkiewicz - Levy (Box 29, Folder 231)
    Lenkiewicz, Steve J. Lenox Hill Hospital Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association Leo, Mrs. Richard Leonard, George E. W. Leonard, Mrs. George Sill Leovigildo Ruiz Le Pair, Jim Lerner-Heller Gallery Lerner, Martin Lerner, Max Lerner, Sandy Leslie, Warren Lesson, Earl E., Jr. Leval, Didier Leval, Pierre Lever Brothers Company Lever House Levin, Jehud Levine, Corine Godfrey Levine, George Levine, Mrs. H. Levitin, Joseph Levy, Julien Levy, Richard C. Levy, Samuel
  - Lewen - Leymarie (Box 29, Folder 232)
    Lewen, Si Lewin, Keith Lewin, Seymour Lewis, Golda Lewis, Joel Lewis, Mary Lewis, Ouida B. Lewitin, Margot Lewthwaite, Margaret Edmonds Leygue, Louis Leymarie, Jean
  - Li Yuan-Chia - Liebmon (Box 29, Folder 233)
    Li Yuan-Chia; Liang, Chengchong Liang; Libby, Erin; Liberman, Alexander; Liberman, Sandu; Liberte, Ruth; Liddle, Nancy; Lieberman, Ira; Lieberman, Ken; Lieberman, William (MoMA); Liebman, Sarah; Liebmon, Mrs. Oscar
  - "LIFE" - Limouse (Box 29, Folder 234)
    LIFE Lightbulbs Light, Robert Light, William H. Lighting Lighting Systems Ligon, Judith K. Ligotti, Dominick M. Limekiller, Dorothy F. Limouse, M.
  - Linares - Lippold (Box 29, Folder 235)
    Linares, Abelardo Linares, Angel Linares, Arturo Lindon, Jacques (Gallery of Modern Art) Linowski, Stella Linsky, Jack Linsky Collection, Jack and Belle Linville, Mrs. Dean Lion, Stephen Liou, Kipaul Lipchitz, Jacques Lipkin, Hilda Lippincott, Donald B. Lippold, Richard
  - List - Lloyd (Box 29, Folder 236)
    List Family Collection Litto, Frank Liu, Mrs. Han H. Liu, Kuo-Sung Livermore, Bruce M. Livingston, R. Crawford Lloyd, Frank Lloyd, Mrs. H. Gates
  - Lobello - Lois (Box 29, Folder 237)
    Lobello, Peter Lochtefeld, John Lockwood, John E. Locus Art Directory Loeb, Albert (Albert Loeb and Krugier Gallery) Loevenich, Karl Loewy, Alexandre Loftus, Nadea Dragonette Logan, Gene Logue, Mrs. Robert W. Lohman, Robert Lois, George
  - Lokitz - Lonigro (Box 29, Folder 238)
    Lokitz, Selma Lokuliyana, Lionel Lolly Studios Lo Moro, Bruno Lonardi, Graziella Longacre, Allan Longcor, Arvilla Longendyke, Adele Long Island Art Festival Lonigro, Betty Peck
  - Loomis - Losert-Schwerzler (Box 30, Folder 239)
    Loomis, Ronald N. Lora, Mario Lorber, Martin Lord, Mrs. Winston Loria, Jeffrey H. Loring, Alta Los Angeles County Museum of Art Los Angeles Times Losbichler, Ludwig Losert-Schwerzler, Hedy
  - Louth - Loy (Box 30, Folder 240)
    Louth, William T. Louviere, Matthew Louvre, Paris Louys, Madame Pierre Loving, Linda Lowe, Maxine Lowenthal, Joan Lowery, Joe Lowy, Julius (Julius Lowy Inc.) Loy, Helen M.
  - Lu - Lytle (Box 30, Folder 241)
    Dr. Lu (Lu Wai-Chuen) Lucas, Grant Ludwig, Anny P. Maria Luisa Aragon Lukas, Julia Lund, David Lund, Toivo Lundgren, Eric Lundgren, Mrs. Herbert Lunning, Elizabeth Lupas, Louis Lupis, Dr. Guis Eppe Lurcat, Jean Lurie, Ranan R. Lustig, Laurance Lynch, Ann Lynch, S. D. Lyndon Baines Johnson Library Lyons, Linda Z. Lytle, Richard Lytle, Dorothy
  - Lacquer Conservation/Restoration, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 242)
    Correspondence, memoranda and lists re items to have their lacquer restored by Mr. Tsujimoto at Museum of Modern Art (MoMA).
  - Legal Releases, 1966-1974 (Box 30, Folder 243)
    Background material on 1966 Fine Arts Law. Correspondence seeking to acquire reproduction rights to items owned by NAR.
  - Legal Releases (A-J), 1966-1974 (Box 30, Folder 244)
    Le Bateau Lavoir Gallery Berge, Dorothy Sister Bianca Galeria Bonino Bouts, Bernard Carr, Louis Galerie Chalette Castelli Gallery Clark, Patrick Galerie Claude-Bernard Cooper, Warren van Doesburg, Mme. Petro Charles Egan Gallery Cordier & Ekstrom Gallery Elkon Gallery Emmerich Gallery Fischbach Gallery Fucina degli Angeli Gambling, William Gemini, Ltd. Gimpel & Weitzenhoffer Goodnough, Robert Goldowsky Gallery Gray, Cleve Guarducci, Otello Guastella, Nick Hayes, David Harrison, Wallace K. Holst, Beate Wheeler Horwitt, Will Hull, John Galerie Im Greichenbeisl Janis Gallery Jones, Frederick
  - Legal Releases (K-R), 1966-1974 (Box 30, Folder 245)